It turns out that a copper wire is added to the lighter.
It also has such a big role
A lot of people don't know
Just think the lighter is for ignition
But tie it to a copper wire.
Its use value is doubled immediately.
Today, let's share it with you
First of all, use a screwdriver to get this copper wire.
Then, at this end.
This end of the line skin.
First, wind a few turns on the screwdriver
When it's wrapped, make it a little tighter.
It will take about four turns.
After it's wrapped like this, then take this off.
Next, use a pair of pliers to repair it a little.
The same is true for the front. Please repair it too.
And then?
Put some tape on the top and bottom of this copper wire.
Use this electrical glue to wrap it around a few times.
You don't need to wrap it too long, just wrap it so much.
Then, you can wrap it in more layers.
OK, let's see.
After the removal, then give him this tape to pull off first.
And then?
We'll tie this to the lighter side.
It's still the same
Use this tape to tie it
When you tie it, you must pay attention to it.
This lighter, this place
Be sure to align this copper wire with this position.
This will tie it firmly.
OK, after a few laps
Cut off the extra bit.
It's a little long here, go a little bit.
So it's made.
Then, let's say hello and try it. First, heat it up.
Heat it for more than ten seconds, let's take a look.
Almost
Then, let's take a look at it in a Chinese sense.
A very simple and easy-to-use lighter electric soldering iron is ready.
Let's see the speed of tin conversion is also very fast, how about it?
And then?
It's like a charger at home.
Or some other electrical appliances, the thread on it is broken.
We can also weld it
The same is true when we use it again.
Heat it up first, huh?
After the heat.
Then it's easy to weld this wire to it.
Well, after heating up, then we'll look at it.
Er, you see, it's as simple as welding, isn't it
And the welding is also very firm
How's it going?
Lighter with a copper wire, its role is not very big
The electric fan at home is broken and the motor does not turn.
What about a situation like this
90% of the above motors are broken.
Encountered this kind of situation
Let's not worry, throw this motor away.
It would be a shame to throw it away.
In fact
We just need to give him a simple treatment and we can fix it.
Then use
Before processing
First of all, we must determine whether it is a motor problem.
It is also very simple to judge whether the motor is good or bad.
First of all, let's turn on the switch for the electric fan.
Then, listen to the buzzing sound on the motor.
If there's a buzzing sound
It means there is electricity on the motor
If the motor does not rotate, it means that the motor is broken.
It's broken
In the future, it will be divided into three situations.
We just need to fix it
First of all, the first
When we were checking the motor
First, turn the rotor by hand.
Let's see if the turn is heavy or not.
It's hard to turn. It's not hard to turn.
What if the turn is particularly heavy
This kind of situation means that the motor is stuck in the shaft.
The reason is ah
On the front and back of its shaft sleeve
Shaft stuck caused by severe oil shortage
All we need to do is take it apart.
Then, casting some lubricating oil on the shaft sleeve can solve this problem.
What about the second case?
When we turn the rotor with this hand, we are very light.
very light
Then, when we turn on the electric fan
The motor just doesn't turn by itself.
When we put our hands together
It started on its own.
What about a situation like this
Generally speaking, it shows that there is something wrong with the above starting capacitor.
As for us, we only need to change a starting capacitor to solve this problem.
The third situation is that after we change the starting capacitor
The motor still can't start by itself
This kind of situation shows that it is a problem inside the motor.
We just need to take it apart
Then deal with it.
can also solve this problem
In fact, like the motor does not turn
This starting capacitor is less bad
Most of them are internal reasons.
We just need to take it apart and deal with it.
First of all, let's tear down the back part of the shake head first.
And then remove the shell
What about after you open it
First of all, check whether this part has this temperature insurance.
Like the previous motor
Most of them have this temperature insurance.
If there are circumstances
Check if it's bad
In fact, there are many bad temperature insurance
What happened after I found it was broken?
All we need is to connect these two thread ends together.
I don't need it
Now, look at many motors that do not have this thing
So say
It is no problem to short together.
If there is no temperature insurance like this
Well, what about this situation
We need to follow these two lines of this capacitor first.
Then go this way
Find the corresponding two thread ends to check if the thread ends are broken.
There are more burnt threads like thread ends.
Because this electric fan is now an aluminum coil.
Where's the aluminum coil?
When it works, it only generates a lot of heat.
Hey.
Look at this wax tube. It's all this color.
It is easy to break when the temperature is high.
After it is broken, it is equivalent to the electric fan without this capacitor.
So, it won't start.
It won't turn
First of all, let's take a look at the two lines of the motor capacitor.
A line is in this position
Well, it just doesn't have a wax tube.
Normal, should be set of wax tube
And then the other line is inside this wax tube.
First, get this rope out of the way.
Then when this dial
Do be a little careful, slow down
Don't break this coil
Then gently pull this away
Good.
Then, let's get this thread out for him first.
Look at it, this joint, this part
Good.
After removing it
Let's take a closer look
Well, this line is the line that starts the coil.
And then it did break
What about a situation like this
Let's wrap it around this terminal again.
And then, you solder it together with an electric soldering iron.
After welding and covering
We then used the original wax tube to cover it and make insulation.
And then?
Give him some glue 502, some glue to fix it.
After this treatment
At the end of the day, let's put this shell on it again.
After loading
Let's pull this motor back and forth.
And then, take another turn
Er...
Let it be active first and see if it is more active.
Hey.
That's it.
If there is anything you don't understand
You can ask me in the comments section.
Let's discuss it together.
Like our home often eat this kind of electric kettle
A year is bad for several
What about a broken kettle like this?
Everybody don't throw
Today, I 'd like to share with you a very useful method.
Actually, we can fix it with a stylus.
What about today's video?
Let's share with you after the electric kettle is broken.
All its fault inspection and maintenance methods
First of all, the electric kettle
After generalization
Its problem is that it is not powered on.
In this case, let's first check the chassis
See if there are any problems
During the inspection?
The main thing we do is to see if the two metal shrapnel inside have collapsed.
Didn't bounce up
What if you find that there is no bounce?
Let's get a toothpick and put it in there.
Give him this copper piece and he will solve the problem.
What if there is no problem with this copper sheet
We're going to check this power cord up there.
What about when you check this wire
method is also very simple
First of all, it's a hand, touching an insert.
Then, I used a magnetic pen to measure these two shrapnel.
Check if this indicator is on.
This one is not bright, so replace it with another one.
Uh...
This light shows that
This line is conducting
Then test another one.
See if the indicator light is on, uh
If it is also bright, it means that there is no problem with this chassis.
Then, let's check this electric kettle.
During the inspection?
First, remove the three screws under the bottom shell.
After disassembling the shell
Let's first look at, uh
What about these two lines above?
It is connected at the position of this switch
Then, we check whether the switch is good or bad.
First of all, put this switch in the open state.
And then what, we unplug the wire from a switch
And then it's the same way.
Uh...
With my hand, touch this line
Then, I used a measuring pen to check it.
In addition, take a look at the straight light on this line.
If it is lit, it means that there is no problem with this switch.
If it is not lit, it means that the switch above is broken.
We can fix the problem by changing the switch for him.
What if there is no problem with this switch
Our next step is to check the coupler above.
In fact
Like this couplant during repair
Its bad is more
The way to check it is also very simple.
First of all, it's the same.
First, touch the copper piece on the coupler with one hand.
Then, measure the upper two circles respectively.
See if this paper lamp is on.
This one inside is not bright, and then measure the one outside.
The one outside is not bright either.
Then, let's measure the coupler.
In addition, this angle will be measured again.
See if it's bright or not
Ah, this is bright, isn't it
Look at the bright outer ring.
This outer ring and this angle are conductive.
Then this corner is not bright, which means we can see that it is not bright or not bright.
That explains the problem
Is goose gas bad
We'll take the goose down first.
And then we look at the reverse side of it.
His bad reason
Just let's take a closer look at the coupler.
is that this corner is not conducting
Let's take a look at the reason, is this corner
This contact on this side of the connection
After a long time, we can see that he has been, uh, burned and deformed.
The two contacts can't touch each other.
In a situation like this, we can change our gas if we have the conditions.
If you do not change the case
I also want it to be used again
You need to put the contacts on this one.
Get him down. Use this screwdriver to pry it.
Let these two contacts contact together
We see that we are in contact now, right
Then, we can install it
This is an electric kettle is not powered on a maintenance method
If the electric kettle is not heated
In this case, first check the heating plate
This is its heating tube
Does the plug of the two wires on the heating tube fall off?
What if there is a problem?
Just plug it in again and plug it in tightly.
If it is still not heated after tightening.
A situation like this shows that the heating pipe is broken.
And then?
After you snap this cover up
Let me share with you again, this electric kettle
In the case that we do not remove the shell
How to quickly judge its good or bad
In fact, the method is also very simple
First of all, look at the two metal shrapnel above, right
First, touch the outer ring with your hand.
Then use that electric pen to measure the inner ring.
See if it's on or not, switch it first.
If he is on, it means the electric kettle is a good one.
If it doesn't light up, it means the kettle is bad.
We see it's already lit, right
The light indicates that the electric kettle has been repaired.
Let's take a look, whether it's a scrapped computer or a scrapped rice cooker at home.
Don't throw away the power cord above
In fact
We just need to use scissors to cut it from the middle, and then
Its use value doubled immediately
First of all
Let's find the middle of this power cord.
Then, we use these scissors to cut it open first.
After the cut, we, uh, separate the ends to the thread.
Then, let's look at this power cord.
What about the two ends of it?
This end is a three-phase plug
The other one is the frequency sub plug.
In fact, these three plugs are more useful in life.
Uh...
And this bottle is so big
It has some special functions in life.
A lot of friends don't know
Today, I 'd like to share with you the usefulness of these two lines in life.
First of all, let's put the end of this line.
Like the power cord on this computer or the power cord on the rice cooker.
Inside it, there are three lines.
After we open it, let's take a look.
Look inside here, there's a brown strip.
A blue
And then there's a green
There is also a yellow greenColor
Like this line, it's the ground line.
And then these two are its zero line and fire line.
Then, we will dial out the lines for it separately.
Boss, all three lines are allocated to it.
After the dial is made, let's take a look.
First of all, give it this thread like twist twist.
Give him a twist first
After twisting it, fold it in half.
fold it in half
The three articles are all the same, what about when they are folded in half?
What can we do with this line first?
Let's see.
If you buy a plug-in strip at home without a power cord
Or the plug on the plug row is broken.
As for us, we can actually connect it with this line.
Then, what about this line?
Because it is three lines, there is a ground line
So it's very safe to connect to this patch.
It works better than some two-wire power cords.
Because it has no ground
So say it's safer without it
We attach it to this patch.
It is very useful when used.
Right?
Well, there's another role.
We can also use it to pick up the power cord on the side appliances at home.
First of all, let's take a look. I have an electric kettle here.
This base
What about the plug above?
Let's see, it's all burned out.
Well, what about a situation like this?
We can actually cut this place off.
And then?
Connect these three wires to it in the same way.
In the future, you can use this plug to continue to use this electric kettle.
The inner diameter of this power cord is very thick
So it is also very safe to use.
Then, let's share it again.
In addition, this part of the pie plug
Its use in life
First of all, we are the same
First, put this side out for it.
The same method is the same
Let's put these three wires out.
After plucking the thread ends
also in the same way
Then twist it to hemp
The flowers are the same after being twisted.
What about this part of the head?
fold it in half
Then, we can take a closer look.
I didn't pay attention just now. Now let's take a closer look at this green line.
In fact, it is a flower color line
There is a yellow bar in the middle
This means that he is a D line.
Then, let's share it with you
Like this kind of plug
It's a special use in life.
First of all, we are still the same
You can first receive it on a row.
After opening the plug-in cover
Be sure to pay attention to this kind of wiring
First of all, let's look at the three terminals on this one, all of which are marked.
This is a D-line callout
Then this one L1 n
Be sure to connect correctly when wiring here.
Don't pick it up wrong
If the wrong connection
This is not edible
We connect these three lines to it separately.
This flower color line is connected to the D line
Then the brown thread is connected to L.
The blue line is connected to N
Tighten the screws separately, be sure to tighten them firmly
After screwing
Then, buckle up the lid on it.
After the production
Let's take a look first, that's what it looks like.
And then like this bottle plug
It's not just this one role
In fact, it has another function.
For example, the electric car charger at home, right
Let's take a look at the end above the battery car
It is also a bottle plug.
Some situations
Often plug and unplug when charging electric vehicles
After a long time of plugging and unplugging
This is prone to loose, poor contact
In fact, we can also
Cut it off
This line can also be connected to this to use good
Now, let's share how to use this gadget.
First of all, we can plug it into an electric car.
What about after you plug it in
Let's first look at the indicator light on the patch, right
If it lights up, it means there is already electricity on it.
We can use it to power electric tools.
For example, these electric drills can be used.
We first plug this power plug into it.
And then to test it
You can turn, right?
Then, we can still use it.
Charging a mobile phone or a charging treasure is very easy to use.
First of all, let's take a look at this charging treasure.
After you plug it in
The indicator light above is not on at present.
Wait, we see it's already lit, right
If it lights up, it means that you can charge the charging treasure.
Also, it can charge the phone.
When the cell phone has no electricity
We can use this thing.
Hey.
No matter where you go, you can recharge it.
Including some power tools
When you go out to work
If there is no 220 power
In fact, we can also plug it into this plug-in to supply power for use.
Do you feel there are any useful methods
We can discuss it together in the comment area.
Mobile phones are not practical after a long time.
When we were using it, we found that it was not turned on.
To charge it, also can't charge electricity
Encountered this kind of situation
Don't worry, spend money to repair
Today, I 'd like to share with you a very useful method.
It can be easily repaired at home.
It first operates the first step
Let's take the slot off the phone first.
Then, we need to remove the back cover
Take a look when removing the back cover.
Some mobile phones have screws on both sides of this charging port.
You need to remove the screws first.
After removing the screw
Then, find a gap and insert it into the corner.
Give it a draw in this circle
You can take this back cover apart.
One circle in place
Then, we can see that the back cover can be removed.
What if a cell phone like this
Let's take a look at both sides of it. There are no screws.
But the back cover is separate from the side.
In this case, when we dismantle it, we can just dismantle this part of the cover.
Just tear down this part
After opening it
Let's first remove the screws from the small plastic cover above.
This mobile phone is a customer.
Because I broke the screen.
So, it's no use putting it on for a long time.
When it wants to repair
I found it and didn't turn it on.
What about a situation like this
Let's fix it first, it can boot normally.
Then, replace the screen.
In fact, this is a common problem of mobile phones.
Not used for a long time
In many cases, the mobile phone will not be turned on.
Charging is not enough
Good to tear down
Then we will remove the little cover on it.
After opening
Then we can look at the three cable sockets above.
We found this little one in the middle
This small one is connected to the battery.
Let's give this battery to it and disconnect it first.
No matter what brand of mobile phone or some digital products
After a long time
The root cause of its failure to charge electricity or boot up
It's caused by the loss of power in this battery.
Now let's test it with a watch.
Look at how many volts it has now.
All brands of mobile phones, its battery socket ah
Most of them are the same.
What about when we measured
Let's take a look at the two thicker points on both sides.
Now it's 3.05 volts
Now, it's only three volts.
This means that the battery has starved to death.
Uh, what about batteries like this?
Generally, after less than 3.5 volts
When we use it, we can't charge it.
This kind of situation shows that
This battery is starving
As for us, we need to force it to be activated before it can be used normally.
The activation tool needed is very simple.
Just need to find one
Scrapped mobile phone charging line
Then, cut off part of the small head and throw it away.
Leave only the part of the USB connector
Then, when I opened it, I found the inside of this
Divided into four
Let's just leave two.
Leaving only black and red
And then like that green and white
We don't need these two data transmission
Just cut it off
No need to use it
Then, put the two lines out of the thread ends respectively.
After the thread ends are plucked, give him this twist first.
Then, in order to better operate
Separate these two lines.
Need to pick up something
Connect a little bit of hard wire or something.
In this way, the operation process will be simpler.
Twist a wire on this
Then, the other line is the same.
Twist a wire forehead, as long as it is hard and small
Screw it up and screw it up.
In fact, this is very simple
The activation tool is made.
Then, at this end.
You can use one, which is used on smart phones.
Be sure to use this kind of charging head on smart phones.
Plug him in
After plugging in
Then, we can use it to give this battery.
Activation fixed
Before activation?
First of all, look at the cable above the battery.
Each battery has its positive and negative poles marked on its cable.
First of all, let's widen the lens.
Take another look
We see there's a label here, too, right?
Then a plus sign on the left side indicates that it is the positive pole.
A minus sign on the right indicates that it is the negative pole.
It corresponds to this plug.
This part of it shows that it is ah
What about this corner on the left
This corner and this corner time are the same
It means that the left side is the positive pole
And then on the right, this is the negative pole.
There's a label here.
According to this label to activate this operation step
First of all, give it the plug and plug it into the plug-in strip.
Then, contact the two lines separately.
Be sure to distinguish between positive and negative poles on the battery socket
Uh, just connect it like this
Uh-huh.
Let him force charge for 30 seconds or a minute first, okay.
It's about a minute now
Then, let's measure it again.
See if there is any change in this voltage.
If its voltage can be charged above 3.5 volts
In fact, the mobile phone can be turned on
As for the mobile phone, the charger that comes with it can also charge it.
Now it's 3.36
This means that the voltage is still a little low.
It also shows that it can be charged normally.
We need to then force recharge it in the same way.
One more minute, one more minute
Then ah
Let's measure it again with a thermometer.
Look at its voltage is now how many volts
3.73, uh, that means this voltage is fine.
Then we'll buckle this battery up to him again.
Test to see if it can be turned on
A shaking sound can be heard
Then we look at the phone has been turned on
It seems that his screen is broken
The next step is to change the screen for it.
Let me share with you today.
When our mobile phone, the password was forgotten
What if I can't open it?
In fact, we can remove this password with one click.
Before clearing the password
First of all, we're going to go into factory mode with our phones.
In factory mode, uh
Below we can clear the password
But the brand of each phone is different
Its entry into the factory mode is probably different.
But it's all the same
What about before we go into factory mode
The first thing we have to do is turn this phone off.
Just press the shutdown button for a long time to shut down first.
We can't enter its factory mode until we finish the machine, so what about after we close the machine?
We began to operate
Entering the factory mode is generally divided into two types.
Uh...
We're here to operate the side keys of the phone.
Let's test this part first.
We can hold down the power button and the volume down button with one finger.
If you want to give it the following while holding it down, let's test it first.
See if you can enter.
Don't let go
See if you can enter
If you cannot enter the case
We're going to come in another way.
Nothing but ah, just these two ways
What about the other one?
We just have to press and hold the volume up button and the power up button at the same time.
Long press do not let go
Good.
Let's take a look and now we are in factory mode.
Let's release these two buttons at the same time.
At the same time, we can have a look after it is released.
This first option, it is to boot
Then the following is to enter this, and the following is the mode of entering the factory.
Then there are also prompts below, right
We can take a look at the following prompt operation
Press the volume up and down keys to make menu selections
Just let's see, the volume up key and down key can be operated without him.
Then and the power key, it is the OK key.
This power key is a confirmation key and has not been operated for 2 minutes.
It has to be restarted
That's why we have to operate quickly.
Some mobile phones can only be operated by side keys.
However, there are also some mobile phones that can also be operated by clicking on the screen.
But it can't be ordered
If we cannot click, we will choose this power-on key.
It is the confirmation key, click to enter
Enter the factory mode immediately
After entering factory mode
We can clear the password with one click.
Let's wait a moment
Good.
Already in, ILook at it.
There are several options here inside.
The first is to install system software
After the mobile phone system broke down
We can also upgrade the system here.
Then the following is the anti-inflammatory system, here is the clear data
The following about machine restart all have
Here we will choose this to clear the data and open it first.
And then there are three options
The first is to clear the cache
The second is to restore all settings
The third is to clear all data
Here, we will choose this to clear all the data.
Choose the last item
Then there is a hint below. Let's take a look.
Clear data in phone system space only
Keep music pictures and other data
We can choose this, this is sure
Clearing data
There's a progress bar here. Just finish it.
This has already shown that the clearing was successful.
Then we click on this to return
After returning, we can also clear the above two items to it.
Here it is, just clear the phone cache
The cache should also be cleaned up.
After cleaning up, the mobile phone will react faster.
Restore all the settings and we'll leave it alone.
Actual
Then, we will start to return this to him.
After returning, let's take a look here. There is a restart.
Let's click to restart
Let the phone restart into its system
Here, this boot, this speed
Slow down a little bit
Because this mobile phone has already cleared the password
cleared its cache
It's all taken care
Therefore, the startup is slower.
This is the first time after the boot, it will be normal
After starting up, the mobile phone will enter the activation interface.
Then just finish the setup wizard
The same as the new phone.
We chose this simplified Chinese first.
Then click agree with the network, we can skip it first.
Just skip it all, okay
Now?
The mobile phone can enter the system with one click.
Let's see if the password is gone, right
The shaver was removed with one click. It took several years to use it.
The blade will become very dull, not sharp at all.
When in use, it is easy to have a beard.
very difficult to use
This time ah
There are many people who choose to replace the cutter head above.
Or replace that one and buy a new razor directly.
Actually, it's not necessary
Today?
Let me share with you a very useful method.
Just give him a simple treatment and repair.
The blade on top will become as sharp as new.
very easy to use
Whether it's the head of this rotary shaver
Or the head of this palace-style razor.
They're all handled in the same way.
First of all, before the operation
Let's get this shield off it.
Uh-huh.
Then, take off the blade inside.
After taking it down
Then I 'd like to share with you his handling methods.
Take this out first
Then, this is the blade inside.
Take out the blade first
Er...
This is this, this rotary cutter head.
And then a reciprocating cutter head like this is actually the same.
Take this lid off.
After you take it down, this side is its blade.
This is a protective net.
Then this processing method
They're both the same
The first thing is to use this toothpaste.
Well, actually toothpaste
It is a grinding function
It can repair the blade
some friends may say, ah
Uh...
This shaver has its own grinding function.
It can automatically grind the blade above
Actually, new.
When ah
It is grinding function, is very easy to use
However, after a long time
There is a gap between the upper blade and the protective net.
What about when the gap gets bigger?
Its own grinding function is no longer useful.
Whether it is rotary or reciprocating, it is the same
After a long time
When this gap between the two of them gets bigger, it won't grind.
So?
We're going to use this toothpaste, give him an auxiliary
Add to his grinding function
They handle it the same way.
The first thing is to squeeze out the toothpaste on this blade.
Hey.
So after the squeeze
Then, buckle up this cover.
Like this, it is the same
Just squeeze it on this filter.
Well, you see, after squeezing here.
Then, give him this blade and put it on.
After putting it on, then install it for them again.
After it is installed, look, just start the razor.
Let it, first so
Well, idling for about 2 minutes
In this way, it can play a very good grinding effect.
Let's see now that this toothpaste has changed color, right?
In the process of grinding
Uh-huh.
Let it grind for about 2 minutes
Uh...
Let's take a look at the blade above.
It changes, ah
Good.
You see, it's 2 minutes now.
Then turn it off, turn it off, and then take this fence off for him.
And then?
Get some water and clean it up
Put this in this
This way, let's remove this cutter head first.
When it is removed, it will be easier to clean it
What's next?
Find an old toothbrush and clean it.
This protective net for him to clean up again
After cleaning up
Take this blade and then install it.
Look, it's very clean.
And this blade is also very bright.
very sharp
Finally, install the protective net on it again.
Listen to the effect.
You see, this way
it is quite sharp
very useful
This shaver, after this treatment
In fact, the effect is the same as that of the new razor.
very good